[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "Tell us -- the latest mood, I guess, that people want to sense is what is President Assad's reaction likely to be to any strike that comes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "That's a very good question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "And there is incontrovertible evidence to that effect?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yes, that debate has actually changed over the past couple of days, as well, and some of the video that we're seeing right now is one of the reasons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "General Kimmitt, from a military perspective, what do you believe is the most likely military action that President Obama will take and how effective, in your experience, do you think it will be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Well, my political judgment is that the administration will not do a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kimmitt", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Adam Schiff, I mean, if that is correct, and that seems to be the perceived wisdom about what may be coming, if it's not going to be that effective and isn't really going to dismantle the Assad regime, which is something that most people have been calling for for quite some time now, what's the point of it other than making some kind of political statement?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Well, I think it will be effective if the object is to deter Assad from using chemical weapons again and to deter others around the world from feeling that this is now the new norm, that chemical weapons are just another tool in the military toolbox.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Adam Schiff"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Syria"]}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJR", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "How dangerous is that for President Obama and indeed other world leaders?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Well, I think the main reason that President Obama has not been more decisive is indeed that the public -- the public has no appetite for some kind of broader international military engagement in Syria.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "And if he is, why are we not trying to seek to change his regime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "That's right, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nick"]}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Can I pipe in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Yes, you can, Nick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hannah"]}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "What do you think happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "In my heart of hearts, I think that Hannah perhaps got herself into a situation that she couldn't get herself out of, and I do believe that my brother gave his life to protect her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Do you really believe that, Laura?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Laura"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Why would he do all this if he was a completely innocent man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Well, let's start with the first thing that you went over, the booby trapping of the house.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "That he was in a shootout with police?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "You don't believe that, either?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Well, I know one thing for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "In Idaho?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Idaho"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "I mean, that's not what a man of his age should be doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Fair enough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hannah"]}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Have you answered that to yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "I know that he thought of Hannah as a daughter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "You were -- you were very close to James?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "How close?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "He was my best friend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["San Diego"]}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "I've got to put that to you that you just don't want to believe that your brother could be capable of such a monstrous act as the police believe he committed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Well, again, we're coming back to -- I'm still seeing no evidence, no -- the sheriffs -- the San Diego sheriffs have basically said that the case is closed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "If it wasn't him, who was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "You think she's just lying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "I'm not going to speak to that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "What do you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "I remember very vividly telling my brother, she's trouble.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Piers, can I stop you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Do you think that was linked in some way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "No, I -- I think that, you know, in many ways, they're very different situations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim"]}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "But was there anything in his behavioral pattern over the years where you thought potentially one day, he could crack up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "You know, the only thing that I could say to that is that Jim was very quiet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 357, "question": "I mean, is it a possibility?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Certainly is a possibility -- anything is a possibility...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "What is your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Well, they have a right to their own opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "And if so, why did you do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "To this day, I have not asked the Andersons.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "And do you intend to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "We'll see when the time comes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Was that a surprise to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "No, it was not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 418, "question": "Did Brett -- did Brett believe that James had done all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "VBD", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "So that was...", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brett", "Brett", "James"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Did he tell you that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "I think he was a little -- he was a little surprised.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Morgan, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "How are you, man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "So you're -- you're now the world's pop expert because you made this movie that the entire world's teenage force is clamoring to watch.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "And so what is -- what is your reaction to the great twerking controversy involving Miley Cyrus?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I think that the fact that you and I are actually having a conversation about it has proven that she accomplished everything she's set out to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley Cyrus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "It's so important, isn't it, to the brands of these young pop stars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Well, I think -- I think the biggest thing you've hit on is that it is a machine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "It's been pretty wild (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Why did you do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "PURLOCK: To have the chance to make like a blockbuster, a -- a documentary blockbuster, a film that would appeal to such a major -- major audience was something I was really excited about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "What do you make of what is happening here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "I mean, and the biggest thing for me is you want to make sure that all the information you're getting is accurate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130827pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "The trust goes, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "And -- and it goes immediately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]